indigocard.com 2019-06-19

# Indigo Platinum | Privacy Policy

This online privacy notice describes how Genesis FS Card Services, Inc. Genesis FS Card Services may collect, use and share information  gathered in connection with your use of this website.  Your use of this website may include, but is not limited to, a prequalification request using this website, an application for credit using this website, and/or other submission of information that you provide when you use this website.This notice is separate from and in addition to the Genesis FS Card Services Privacy Policy and the Privacy Policy and the On-Line Privacy Notice of the issuer of any credit card for which you apply via this website or another website.

**Online Tracking of Your Use of Website and Information We Collect**

So that we may better serve your needs, we and our third-party providers (when applicable) monitor your use of our website(s) and those of our third-party providers (when applicable). In using such website(s), you acknowledge that we do not filter traffic to block monitoring of your use in response to do-not-track signals or mechanisms external to our systems.

Genesis FS Card Services collects two types of online information: Non-Personal Information and Personal Information.

_Non-Personal Information:_  When you visit our website, we collect the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. In addition, we collect other information such as what browser type you are using, the type of operating system you have, and what website you may have come from and other information from your device settings. We may also collect navigational information such as pages visited and time spent on a particular page.

When you browse our website or respond to one of our emails, Genesis FS Card Services may use cookies, pixel tags, Flash objects, web beacons, clear GIF’s or other technologies to collect information and store your online preferences. Cookies are widely used and most browsers are set up to accept them automatically. If you would prefer, you can choose to not accept cookies. If you prefer not to accept cookies, you can :

  * Change your browser settings to notify you when you receive a cookie, which lets you choose whether or not to accept it;
  * Set your browser to automatically not accept any cookies.

_Personal Information:_  In addition to the information described above, we may also gather personal information that you provide, such as: your name, address, phone number, email, social-security-number, and/or date-of-birth. For example, we collect personal information when you submit a prequalification request or apply for a new program or account. We may gather your product choice or other preferences and selections along with this personal information and we may connect your personal information to the Non-Personal Information that we also gathered.

If Genesis FS Card Services has other personal information about you, or information that is publically available from other sources, we may use it in combination with the information we collect on-line.

The information collected through this website is held by Genesis FS Services.

**How Does Genesis FS Card  Services Use the Information We Collect**

Genesis FS Card Services may use the information collected in connection with this site in one or more of the following ways:

  * To recognize return visits to this site or visits to any other website that Genesis FS Card Services or its affiliates or third-party providers (when applicable) owns or operates
  * To provide information, products, and services that you request
  * To facilitate credit card prequalification requests and/or credit card applications initiated through the site
  * To improve your experience of the site
  * To contact you regarding products and services (1) that Genesis FS Card Services offers and (2) that third parties offer
  * To provide to third parties that may contact you regarding offers of products and services
  * To share your information with third parties for data processing or other business in relation to services or information that you request
  * To share your information with third parties whose products and services you request

Genesis FS Card Services may provide your information to third parties (unaffiliated with Genesis FS Card Services, Inc.) and our affiliates, including but not limited to selected third party marketers and vendors as well as third party contractors providing services to Genesis FS Card Services for the operation of the Site and its business, communication services, and fulfillment of orders.

**Requests to Limit Sharing**

To limit our sharing of your personal information, please refer to the Genesis FS Card Services Privacy Notice and the instructions provided on how to limit our sharing.

Please be aware, if you request to limit our sharing of your personal information as described in the Genesis FS Card Services Privacy Notice, but thereafter, you request a service or product that requires us to share your information with a third party to process your request, then your previous request to limit our sharing of your personal information will not apply to your request for such service or product.

**Notice of Changes**

From time to time, we may change this notice. The effective date of this notice, as stated below, indicates the last time this notice was revised or materially changed. Your use of the site following these changes means that you accept the revised practices.

**Effective Date**

**Rev.** 08/14

....................................................................................................................................................................................................................................
